Okay.
I just wanted to confirm while you're here now and we can be in public,
just the question that I asked last Monday about type fours
at stations like Palmer and New Plymouth, and if they are out of action, but
they respond with a type three, do they pick up the type four call
sign,
with a no letter? And the second part was your response that they'd
have a four-six-four ladder. And I just wanted to confirm those two aspects.
Sure. Thanks, Mr. Costley. So when-- It doesn't seem like only
a week ago we had a chat, does it?
So what I spoke to you about last hearing was the
national procedure of what we should do.
So you asked me whether I can give assurance that that always happens, and I
can't give you assurance that it always happens, because
procedure isn't always followed.
Now, there may be good reasons for that, so we deal with that
as it goes. But the procedure I spoke to you about is best
practice. Your call sign should reflect your
capability, so an incident controller can understand
what's on route.
Understood. And
stations that have a type four, do they have a four-six-four ladder?
Not all of them, no. So they don't have it. They're waiting in the wings.
So
you will know through our figures, there's 19 type fours.
Right.
There are five stations that have a type three with the
four-six-four ladder in that station.
Of the 19?
Correct. As part of the normal fleet for that station.
Okay.
Righty. Well, thank you. Thank you very much for that, and that will bring us to
the end of our time with you. Yeah